[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "So what does Sharon Bialek think now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "He has no one to blame but himself.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon Bialek"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What do you think -- when it comes to the election battleground that you're a pivotal member of the -- of the Obama campaign, when you see this divide now being so clearly laid out, what do you think the average American is going to think of the debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me just correct one thing you said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican Party"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Or has the president not played his hand very well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, I think that the Republican Party has made a decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What went wrong with the way that America used to do business so successfully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, let me say a few things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Where are you most critical on yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, you know, I think part of -- if I were -- I'm not going to speak for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Who do you, when you're planning your campaign, most fear and perhaps are most, you know, looking forward to taking on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJS", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "RBS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, it's hard to read because, as you say, it's been a really volatile situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "If I can give you Gingrich or Romney to take on the president, who would you prefer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, you know, I want to watch this because I'm learning things about them every day, and it's a very interesting race.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Sharon, what was your reaction when you heard that Herman Cain was suspending his campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Piers, you know me, you might think that I might have been elated at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "And you know the general feeling you got by the end was, well, he's only going because of the terrible media reporting all these outrageous lies, but it's not as simple as that, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "No, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "I mean what is your financial position and has any of the motivation for what you've done been driven by the need for money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "ORGAN: Were you surprised to see, Gloria, Herman Cain's wife smiling and holding his hand as if nothing had happened given the volume of women who came forward with either harassment claims or in the case of Ginger White, the affair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "No, Piers, I was saddened for her, and I'm sure that she's very hurt in all this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria", "Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "I mean do you accept as some of Herman Cain's supporters say, indeed I interviewed his attorney Lin Wood about this, that there remains no hard evidence to substantiate what you say and in the end people have to kind of work out who they believe, you or him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "You know, I listened to you last week, Piers, with the Lin Wood interview.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Do you worry about the repercussions now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Why are Americans so obsessed with weather?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNPS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, because unlike Britain, we actually have weather.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Somewhere in America at any given time there is this extremity of weather, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "There really is and -- which is why this is a great job.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Poppins"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "JJS", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "``", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Why do you think people love to hear bad news, which it normally is, from Al Roker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Well, because I think, you know, it's kind of like -- again, another one of your well -- best loved Brits, Mary Poppins, I think once said, \"a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down, the medicine go down, the medicine go down.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Here's the deal: believe me, if I thought I was putting my life at risk, seriously, I would not do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Geraldo"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And what would happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I remember seeing Geraldo in the middle of a hurricane out to sea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "And I wanted to Tweet into the show saying get out of the water would be plan B, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "There is that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "How long have you been here, Piers, in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I've spent about four months of a year here until this year.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What do you make of what's going on politically in your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, look, you know, it's one of these things that I think I feel bad for Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "It's about time they renamed that place the Roker-feller center, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I've been trying to get them to do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "What do you personally feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, look, personally, from just a standpoint -- from an American standpoint, from being an American, seeing this happen I think was just a momentous occasion in this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "To quote a famous chat show star in America, what was she thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "You know, it was a bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "It's going to be stormy today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What do you do to unwind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "We do the same things everybody does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "I want to come back after the break, Al, and talk about your book, this sinister tone that appears to be -- unless I'm wrong -- a kind of metaphor for you wanting to murder Matt Lauer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Lauer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Does the president have to worry about the boxing part?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Sometimes when he sees me punching, he kind of --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "You were gigantic, weren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I was huge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Lauer"]}, "docId": "111205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "It's clearly a euphemism for you wanting Matt Lauer's job, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "No, Matt Lauer can have his job.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Lauer"]}}]